Hello.
こんにちは
how are you?
元気ですか?
I'm fine.
元気です
Your socks are cute.
靴下がかわいいね
It's like Totoro.
トトロみたいなやつです
It says Miffy.
ミッフィって書いてあるけど
Hey, it's cute.
ちょっとね、かわいいっすね
not at all.
全然
Are you an idol or something?
アイドルとかやってる?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
I'll ask you a lot of questions.
いろいろ質問しちゃうね
How old are you now?
今は何歳ですか?
10 years old
10歳
is.
です
You're going to school.
学 校行ってるんだね
How old are you?
何年生?
I'm a second year student.
2年生です
Are you closed today?
今日はお休み?
Yes, I'm off.
はい、お休みです
If you are surprised, suddenly turn the camera.
びっくりしたら急にカメラ回して
get nervous?
緊張する?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張します
Well, I like taking pictures of cute girls.
ちょっとね、かわいい子撮るのが好きなんでね
That's good.
いいよね
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
What do you enjoy most?
一番何が楽しい?
I enjoy lunch time.
お弁当の時間が楽しいです
Lunch box?
お弁当?
It's fun, lunch time.
楽しいよね、お弁当の時間
Are you going to make it?
作っていくの?
I will make it myself.
自分で作っていきます
By yourself?
自分で?
Not at my mother's place.
お母さんのとこじゃなくて
Eh, I don't need it.
え、いらないね
Are you going to make Manias?
マニアス作るの?
I'll make Manias.
マニアス作ります
Do you enjoy eating out with friends?
友達と一緒に食べる時間が楽しい?
yes.
はい
Nice, it's youthful.
いいね、青春だね
I see, do you have any club activities?
そう か、部活とかやってる?
I'm doing club activities.
部活やってます
I'm playing barrier ball.
バリアボールやってます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's an athletic club.
運動部なんだ
Because I like exercise.
運動好きなので
I like the style.
スタイルいいもんな
There's no wasted meat.
無駄な肉はないもんね
That was surprising.
意外だったね
I wonder if I'll try some fruit or something?
何かフルーツとかやってそうかな?
I can't play musical instruments.
楽器はできないです
Can't play musical instruments?
楽 器はできない?
I see.
そうか
You'll be popular at school, right?
モテるでしょ、学校で
Is it ok?
まあまあですか
Well, that's pretty much it, then.
まあまあって相当だね、じゃあ
Are you dating anyone now?
今付き合ってる人とかいるの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Have you been there before?
これまではいた?
Until now, there was one person.
これまでは1人いました
Is there only one person?
1人だけなんだ?
How long have you been dating this person?
この人はいつからいつまで付き合った?
It's been a week since we started dating.
付き合ってから1週間で
Hurry up?
早くね?
It's early.
早いです
why?
なんで?
I understand because we were both busy.
お互い忙しかったので分かりました
When do you say you're busy?
忙しいっていつの話?
It was when I was in junior high school.
中学生の時です
It's not that busy, really.
忙しくないだろ、本当に
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Sad memories.
悲しい思い出
So, did you do that with that boyfriend?
ってことは、その彼氏とはそういうことをした?
Well, I tried to do it, but I stopped halfway through.
まあ、しようとしたんですけど、途中でやめました
Have you stopped?
やめちゃった?
Yes, I quit.
はい、やめました
Why did you stop?
なんでやめたの?
It means let's stop.
やめようってことです
Let's both stop.
お互いやめようって
Well, the other side calmed down with that.
よく向こうがそれで落ち着いたね
I managed to calm down.
なんとか落ち着きました
Were you scared?
怖かったりしたんだ?
Yes, just a little bit.
はい、ちょっとだけ
Because it was my first time.
初めてだったから
When will you do it for the first time?
いつ初めてはするの?
I haven't done it yet, so I'm done.
まだしたことないので、終了です
yes?
そう?
You said it clearly.
はっきり言ってくれたけど
Seriously?
マジで?
Have you never done it?
したことないの?
Yes, no.
はい、ないです
Oh, that's a bit difficult.
あら、それちょっと大変だね
yes.
はい
It's a special time, isn't it?
とくときだね、それは
Is it okay for the first time?
初めて、大丈夫?
This is your first time, right?
初めてするんでしょう?
I'm nervous.
緊張します
Did you ever feel like graduating?
ちょっと卒業してみたいな気持ちはあったの?
there was.
ありました
I see.
そうか
But isn't that what makes you popular?
でもモテるわけでしょ?
There are plenty of opponents, right?
相手はいくらでもいるでしょ?
yes.
はい
Hey, why don't you meet someone like that?
ねえ、そういう人とはしない?
of school.
学校の
I don't.
しないです
why?
なんで?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
Well, I'll teach you carefully today.
じゃあ今日は丁寧に教えてあげるね
thank you.
ありがとう
Suddenly.
急に
It's scary, isn't it?
怖いですよね
That's not Totoro.
トトロじゃないよ、それ
Miffy.
ミフィ
It says Miffy.
ミフィって書いてあるもん
I thought I heard it.
耳に立ったかと思いました
Is that so?
そういうこと?
This is all I know too.
俺もこれしか知らないけど
Wow, her face is so small.
すごい、なんか顔ちっちゃ
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Have you ever held hands?
手つないだことあるでしょ?
there is.
あります
What about kissing?
キスとかは?
did?
した?
I did.
しました
tomorrow?
明日?
How far did you go?
どこまでしたの?
I did it before I put it in.
入れる前までしました
入れる前までしたんだ
Did you try to include it?
入れようとはしたの?
I tried to put it in, but it hurt a little so I stopped.
入れようとはしたんですけど、 ちょっと痛かったからやめ
I did.
ました
Oh, it hurt a little.
あ、 ちょっと痛かったんだ
nice.
いいね
Because it's cute.
可愛いから
I'll look at it.
眺めちゃうね
Such an elegant
こんなお上品な
It's cute, in casual clothes.
可愛 いね、私服ね
Can I take this off for a second?
ちょっとこれ外していい?
I've never done it though.
一回もしたことないけど
Totoro.
トトロ
Miffy.
ミフィ
It says Miffy.
ミフィって書いてある
Maybe I should write what I hear.
耳書いちゃおうかな
Miff
ミフ
I.
ィ
what happened?
どう したの?
It's a bit like Totoro, my uncle.
ちょっとトトロでさ、 おじさんがさ、
Stimulate Totoro here
ここトトロを刺激して
Very kind.
すごい 優しい
why?
なん で?
gently.
優しく
Was it touched?
触られた?
I was touched.
触られた
Your breasts are beautiful, their shape.
おっぱい綺麗だね、形
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Why do you touch it?
なんで触るの?
Like a small animal.
小動物みたいに
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
difficult.
難しい
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
But she's a really cute person.
でもすごい可愛い人に
Did you buy it yourself?
自分で買ったの?
I bought it because it was different.
違うんで買いました
Just like that.
そのままさ
knees.
膝
Can I get on my knees?
膝つけちゃっていい?
Here.
ここに
oh yeah.
そうそう
So, push me out.
で、押し付き出して
Look here.
こっち見て
She has a beautiful body.
綺麗な体してるんです
It feels weird.
変な感じが
変な感じ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことあるでしょ?
Did you get licked?
舐められた?
It's still hidden.
まだ隠れてるよ
Have you ever had your fingers inserted?
指入れられたことある?
Didn't you put your finger in?
指入れなかったの?
I couldn't get in.
入れなかった